Good evening, brothers! Good evening, come and see Dabei tonight. Tonight, Dabei sixty-one point six,
I will fuck you until fifty-five, so I can only do it with the first blow. What kind of equipment do you have?
Why are you carrying a bag in there?
Black card! Don't come to Eight Ten, just a black card, brother. Black card. I feel like I can throw away my bag.
This head can also be sold for sixty.
This one already costs 6.3 million! Ah, spaceflight is so fun. I want to play in spaceflight bases for the rest of my life.
It’s over and the packet loss is gone. That’s all due to packet loss. Who is this? Water friends, water friends, let’s go.
What are you taking? What are you taking? I'm ready to throw.
It doesn’t mean anything! You're calling a large number. Why are you targeting me? The drone was shot down,
Why are your teammates hitting me? That's right, the number is the big one! Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey!
What does your Veyron teammate mean by this?
It's not him. The main thing is that two people don't fight and one person fights. I don't understand what he means?
That should be a wild card. This is a spirit rat that has been hungry for thirteen minutes.
Now he's waiting for the zipline's enemies to let down their guard. As an astronaut, he walked on his knees,
Well versed in the hunting laws of this land.
Ah! ah! The three-tailed dragon is still Liu Tao. ah! ah! Don’t be tired of listening, brother, I’m for you, I’m for you,
Treat you like this.
There are three groups of teammates, is it true or false? Let me take a look, those three mighty dragons really come from three groups. Hahahahaha!
A little fat! Next time, remember to come early and give me a blast! You should blow it up for me earlier,
Once you and I have a clear picture, we will be happy!
Once broken, Wolong emerges from the mountain; two companies become famous in one battle; three companies are enemies in the world. Come, sit right, brother,
Take off! Come on, ask Brother Ma to do two things, come and do two things in aerospace.
My prison. Hello, Hello, Captain, here I come! Come on, come on, I'm ready.
A team on the bridge, a team on the bridge, coming over, coming over, face. Another one, another one,
Move him, this is also in front.
Yeah, brother, freeze, freeze, freeze, it's here, it's already here. How cruel! He held out the sword,
Let me freeze, otherwise I will swing my sword on my head. I, I, I will help you pull one out. It’s not very safe here.
Pull out quickly, pull out quickly! I was surrounded by dragons, there were enemies, leaks, leaks. Ah, brother, ah, one more.
Flash! Someone, oops, sprayed it! This one will hit you! With him, he hit the brother with one blow!
Beautiful, they are rescued over there, are they rescued over there? No, I can save my brother, I can make up for it,
Empty space in the open space.
So beautiful! You are so courageous, brother, just stop, and there is money, I will bet that he can't beat you.
You are safe next to me, brothers and brothers are safe next to you. Damn it, why are you so fat? No more courage.
You can give it to him, okay, pay five, let's try to go shopping again. It's okay,
There are five more guns on the bridge, brother. I have five more guns hidden over there on the bridge. Throw it away after sending it, brother.
It's definitely available, brother, it's definitely available, brother, it can't be like this. You here, here,
Come here, brother, I will give you the Garao area and you can eat it.
I'm going to make a fool of myself!